galagiveaways.com 2016-12-04

# Indiegala - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important, so INDIEGALA, SRL. ("INDIEGALA," "we," "us," or "our") has created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit the Service, why we collect it and how it is used. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of the Service; it does not apply to other online or offline INDIEGALA sites, products or services. The terms "you," "your," and "yours" refer to the customer/purchaser utilizing our Service. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms and Conditions. By using the Service, you consent to the data practices prescribed in this statement. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy that we will include on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms and Conditions.

#### What Information Is Collected? 

Personally Identifiable

"Personally Identifiable Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number or other contact information, whether at work or at home. INDIEGALA collects the following Personally Identifiable Information from you when you use our Service: your email address, and payment information (credit card and address, PayPal, or Amazon information). If you correspond with us by email or through the Service, we may retain the content of your messages, your email address and our responses. INDIEGALA also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Company help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Service. A cookie may also convey information about how you browse the Service to us. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

#### How Is Such Information Used?

We use the data that you provide or we collect to provide you the services offered on our Service. INDIEGALA uses your email address to email you a link to your game download page and to notify you of future INDIEGALA promotions if the "Notify me about future INDIEGALAs" checkbox is checked. INDIEGALA uses the data you enter on the Service, such as the price you enter and your slider positions, to make sure that your contributions go to the right places. INDIEGALA uses browser data like which operating system you are using to improve user-experience by making your download page default to the game builds corresponding to your current operating system. INDIEGALA may use the site data collected to produce general and anonymous statistics about consumer behavior. We use cookies to improve our Service and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Cookies from our Service can not be read by other sites. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. We may use certain information about you internally for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing content.

#### Is The Information Shared or Disclosed?

INDIEGALA does not sell or share the information it collects hereunder except as described in this Privacy Policy. Information collected from you is disclosed and used to complete and support your purchases from and use of the INDIEGALA Service and to comply with any requirements of law. For example, we may disclose information to third party payment processors. We may also disclose information to third party social networks at your direction, e.g. when you "tweet" or "like" something on the Service. From time to time, we may run contests, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on the Service together with a third party partner. If you provide information to such third parties, you give them permission to use it for the purpose of that Event and any other use that you approve. We cannot control third parties' use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events. INDIEGALA may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on INDIEGALA or the Service; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of INDIEGALA; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of INDIEGALA, its web sites or the public. If INDIEGALA or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that INDIEGALA goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of INDIEGALA may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Choice

You can access and modify your information by visiting your unique download page and changing the settings. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy and the choices you make on the Service will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to INDIEGALA in the context of other, separately operated, INDIEGALA products or services.

#### The Security of Your Information

INDIEGALA has taken measures to protect the security of your personally identifiable information and does not display it on the Service or on your personal download page. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to INDIEGALA or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

#### International Transfers

Personal information collected on the Service may be stored and processed in the Italy or any other country in which INDIEGALA or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

#### Children

INDIEGALA will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person age 13 and under. INDIEGALA encourages parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their children may contact our [support team](http://support.indiegala.com/) to obtain a record of any information held by INDIEGALA and have it removed at their request.

#### Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### Your Consent To This Privacy Policy

By using this Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting Privacy Policy provision. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on this Service which it is your responsibility to review. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

#### Contacting INDIEGALA

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of INDIEGALA, please contact our [support team](http://support.indiegala.com/).
